If you have been watching the news for the last couple of every day for seven months you might be thinking this is it
Baby, hold me
You have nothing to fear
Hypothetically, there are several ways the world can end. I will now tell you why in practice
They will not happen killian will this video? Cause existential dread?
No
Quite the opposite that's german behavior
bloody germans
Scaring people. Ah, the world is terrifying like a way to bring in a burnt vinaign itself ignore them
You need a friendly loving huggable swede to tell you that everything is going great and will go great forever
So let's start with something fun and positive total nuclear annihilation
I
Want to describe how a nuclear workers happen, but then I am become
Demonetized so I can't use any real
Examples, so instead i'll go and use some objects from the kitchen
um, okay, so
what if
saffron
and honey
Decided to go to war and this forces ketchup and caviar to also enter
But meanwhile, they're fighting basmati rice. Oh youtube. No
Most life would be eradicated
Sadly not everyone not cockroaches
And they've made milk from cockroaches
That means human survivors would have access to cockroach yogurt and cockroach cheese if cheese exists
It's not even a post-apocalyptic dystopia
And because the earth will be inherited by doomsday preppers
Severe paranoia will be added to the entire human gene pool
The next human generation won't see any point in nuclear wars because everyone will own bunkers
Irregardless of perpetrators chile will always survive
Do not congratulate them, the entire country itself is thousands of nukes on top of each other
but we like to call them boom mountains the masterpiece 2012 the road and
mistborn these share pretty much the same story super volcanoes cover the world in ash
The most active one is yellowstone, which is supposed to go off
Tuesday, making the us and canada uninhabitable
Okay
That sounds like a you problem
Unfortunately for the sophisticated world, this would create a type of nuclear winter. That's great. That means
Extermination from volcanoes is actually impossible
It's instead because of an ice age
The streams stop moving and there's like a tsunami humans try to find a solution to global warming and freeze the planet
And charlie builds a train canon or a norwegian woman tired of quarantine decides to kill everyone
All three equally possible and they have the same result
No more cheap winter jackets during summer time if I understand the science correctly
They're probably not gonna make a sixth one, but nature science has created an artistic rendition of a real ice age
We can see that this is the worst thing that could happen to earth. I am actually not worried
We can fix all the problems an ice age would cause even on a global scale. We would just have to
Gather close thus it won't lead to an extinction
It will lead to the best thing ever
dystopian mega cities colossal vertical greenhouses
Dark, deteriorating buildings giving heat allowing the last remembrance of man to survive
The air filled with suit from the power plants required to hit the massive penthouses of the ridge
Drooling i'm sorry. It's so beautiful
I'm already breaking my promise claiming an ice age might not happen. I I can't do that to myself
Now that I think about it our most formidable enemy would actually excel during an ice age toaster uprising
the robots taking over humanity
Is guaranteed a robot algorithm already completely rules me and my colleagues
And lets me tell you it's great. I love the algorithm
Though them exterminating us is another story the biggest threat to i.t
Security is the human error. Therefore the human error needs to be eliminated
and so it goes robots would use war to exterminate us because while they are information gathering
They will come across this video and find out all other ways are pointless and I think in a war with robots
We would destroy them
They would always calculate our perfect tactic for every battle and us humans would instead do something too stupid to foresee
Maybe not maybe they have the ability to know our every move hype for advanced self-learning from us humans
And what would they learn?
Yes to be racist
We all remember what happened to tay ai the robots will never defeat us because they will be too busy hating
Robots from production lines in other continents and because I have now proven the only winning move is not to try they won't try
This can't happen. They are too logical but what if the enemy wasn't logical?
Your first reaction is most likely zombies aren't profitable anymore, why would big pharma create them they won't
But if someone eats a winged rat and the disease makes you want to travel
Eventually, they are going to hit something that makes you want to eat someone unlike other things i've mentioned
Zombies are a very limited resource in the first five seasons of the walking dead franchise the walking dead
They killed 1 000 zombies. They're like 20 people
If every 20 people killed 1 000 zombies over two years would have zero zombies after three
In the last of us, it's brain mushroom zombies in the last of us two, okay?
Never played it but thousands of spoilers have been shared with me
Not one of them mentioned zombies so i'm assuming they're gone. That's why some media try to buff them make them run really fast
Give them boss zombies to help these are irrelevant because winters would always destroy their brains
If we have winters the loblal
Warming I can't imagine the world after global warming because there are no good films to show me that
The closest thing we have is interstellar
And they call it a total ecological collapse sounds way scarier than global warming. It's like
Cozy sauna for the planet how to fix global warming fix number one get people to be responsible
No, I remember seeing google's electric car and thinking
It's not worth it. Let's just all die and electric cars for people with self-respect are super expensive
Fix number two air conditioners are expected to go from one billion to five billion in
2050. That means it keeps quintupling every 40 years. We should have 108 billion in 2400
Euros has five queen trillion tons of air on average refrigerates one ton per hour 24 times a day times 180 billion
4.3 trillion a day that
not gonna work
We can't cool the planet with air conditioners. If no one did the math. We would never know fix number three
I don't know any dutch people
Maybe we should consider unleashing more greenhouse gases until we hit the peak so it doesn't stress us out anymore
We won't starve from the ecological disaster because we can just eat all the animals that die
solved
unless
This would cause us to eat warm-blooded animals during lent
That could cause the actual apocalypse
Do you own a twitter?
Then this one will seem the most likely in the most
influential work of all time all life ends because of a ring in space but in the second most influential it ends more
Badass I don't even have to guess how it's gonna go down
It's been perfectly described first a trumpet sound
not specified how just
Wonderfully, so they won't be using a stock sound to save money. I hope it's a jazz trumpet solo
The loyal will be summoned to heaven the loyal sounds like a legal nightmare
So they're probably just gonna summon everyone who hasn't broken the 10 commandments
to avoid litigation which
means I
I won't be joining you I don't
want to admit this but
I have
Worked on sundays. I'm, sorry, you know with with this job days flow together
thus me and a bunch of dudes who cheated on their wives will be stuck in a dogless world because all
Dogs go to heaven and it will have the coolest music this apocalypse has inspired the best music
And while you guys are up there in heaven playing croquet or whatever. We are gonna watch
Michael's sword fighter dragon with seven heads. It's not even gonna be a real apocalypse
I'm, not even gonna stop making youtube videos just change them to appeal more to angels
This was supposed to be a science video
Okay
fine some dumb space shit a muscular philosopher with a high sperm count once said
It doesn't matter what you do the universe will whoop your ass though. It could itself get its ass whooped in several ways
And we could come up with more ways if hard sci-fi wasn't too boring for general audiences
No need to worry about any of this
Hot take the universe is immense
So there has to be someone out there looking out for stuff like this. It's so big
In fact, it's most likely not even a fancy job, you know
Some of the people stopping the universe from ending are currently on union strikes really terrifying their bosses
on the other hand local dumb space shit
They will ignore local dumb space shit a comet is headed towards terra comets are made of ice
Salt melts ice so if it hits the ocean we should be fine
But what if it's a giant asteroid nasa said they would require five years to launch an anti-asteroid operation
That was in
2013. We've been safe for two years
The sun though, it can grow hot it can explode it can freeze according to scientists
The sun is more fragile than a human baby it once shot a laser at mars and destroyed it hasn't happened to us so far
Though that could very well be because we've sacrificed humans to it something we recently stopped doing
The governments might need to reconsider this
Anti-sacrifice stance then we would be completely safe from space
Unless it kills us immediately after I finish this sentence
Oh, thank god
I guess the professionals know what they are doing
Oh, no, I shouldn't have said that it might have given them the impression that we don't know what we're doing alien invasion. If a
Hyper-advanced alien species wanted to annex us they could just park in their atmosphere and tell us to surrender or die
And we would surrender so heck with fighting. I don't understand undercover alien conspiracies
This isn't warhammer 2020 i'm not gonna lift a finger to battle cynos if they want my ps4 or whatever on the other hand
If they want to exterminate us by for example destroy resources
We need to survive or cooler aliens would send giant monsters. I might consider fighting in a giant mech
Though I probably won't have to i've seen american films and they seem pretty confident that if an alien fleet attacks
They got this I choose to believe them if there's one thing I trust it's the us government
worst case scenario
They show up tomorrow declare a martial arts tournament to decide our fate and we can't do it because we are social distancing. No
They're supposed to be smarter than us. They won't plan an event during a pandemic
So let's talk about what you really are here for pandemic
Don't demand on me youtube. I know your first question is it toilet paper will toilet paper save us?
Let's look at the facts. I own toilet paper
I never got the virus everyone. I know who owns toilet paper never got the virus
The only person I know that did get the virus lived in resort seasonal worker housing
That means he did not own toilet paper the resort did
so
No toilet paper won't help I have to clarify so youtube. Don't flag me for
Misinformation but believing misinformation is the reason we will survive a pandemic
you all know a friend or a friend that kept going to parties and was never affected because
Whichever divine being that rules over us be it god or faith. It sure loves people who make stupid decisions
Lemmy smoked a pack of cigarettes and drank one bottle of jack daniels every day and died of prostate cancer
If this current pandemic had gone perfectly. I know this is what would take us
But it didn't so it can't now finally let me tell you how the world will actually end. The only logical end
sadly
Everything has to come to an end even humanity
It will be a happy end though and it has already started with steam allowing adult games
There's now so much capital in the genre. They will eventually fund the perfect vr experiences
And waifus can't bear children. What about women? They are less likely to invest time in such lewd filth
true, but if you haven't noticed every book genre that exists has been
Subjugated by the romance horde you search new cyberpunk books
And the best seller is going to be like evil party leader with a six-pack wants to mass surveillance humanity
Because he's a total alpha but he's soft when he's with this one girl. Now, he'll show her why they call him dictator
I bet you want to read that. I appreciate my videos because I have options but
Fictional shape-shifting soft alphas can't sire children in some books. They can bear them. But the point is this is the way the world ends
not with a bang but with noises of ecstasy some whimpering but if it happens when 10 seconds after you finish this video so long
And thanks for all the comments